https://www.cascadecarnivores.com/privacy.php

Home » Privacy Notice
My Account  |  Cart Contents  |  Checkout  |  Sitemap
Catalog
American Pitcher Plants (7)Bladderworts (6)Butterworts (53)CephalotusCobra Plants (3)Dewy Pine PlantsPygmy Sundew GemmaeSundewsTropical Pitcher PlantsVenus FlytrapsOther Carnivores (1)Seeds (3)Supplies (11)
Quick Find
Use keywords to find the product you are looking for.Advanced Search
Privacy Notice
Your Personal Information
Your personal information is just that, personal.
The information which you enter
on the Cascade Carnivores website is kept private and confidential. The owners and
staff of Cascade Carnivores will never provide to any other parties, freely or for
monitary or other gain, any personal data collected on this website.
The Electronic Nature of eCommerce
For the purpose of allowing you to purchase merchandise online, we deal with
our business partners through electronic means.
Whenever you provide us with personal
account information this is transmitted between you and our server electronically.
Data Encryption
You can be confident that all sensitive information is sent using R4 128-bit
SSL encryption technology.
You will notice the use of our secure server by the lock
symbol in your browser window.
Also, the url address of our site which will change from http:
to https: whenever you are on screens which display sensitive data.
Cookie Usage
For the purpose of monitoring traffic to this web site, we use a cookie that collects
anonymous traffic data only.
There is no personally identifiable data collected.
Thank You
We thank you sincerely for the trust that you place in us by doing business on our site.
Shopping Cart
0 items
Bestsellers
01.Cascade Carnivores' All-Mineral Pinguicula Mix - 1 Quart02.Pinguicula cyclosecta03.Pinguicula agnata red leaf04.Pinguicula jaumavensis05.Dewy Pine Seed
Specials
Pinguicula ehlersiae x oblongiloba$16.00$10.00
Information
Picture GalleryBlogCare SheetsContact UsPrintable CatalogPrintable Catalog-textShipping InformationShipping CalendarPrivacy NoticeConditions of UseCustomer TestimonialsProduct Reviews
Thursday 10 December, 2020
5545387 requests since Thursday 29 December, 2005
Copyright © 2015 Cascade CarnivoresPowered by osCommerce
